(All people, organizations,
locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
Yoon Seo. Are you okay?
Before the last vote closed,
Police used their Skill.
During the night, Park Ji Soo...
was executed by Mafia.
Park Ji Soo was a Citizen.
All participants,
identify the Mafia and begin to vote.
It's on again.
Can we even get out of here?
We must.
Let's find a way out and go home.
Yes.
Let's go outside.
Ji Soo.
Ji Soo, no.
(Let's Focus on Safety!)
Why did you want to see us all?
"Park Woo Ram was Mafia."
See? What did I tell you?
Ko Kyung Jun has a great hunch.
What's the Police doing?
Learn from him.
Did you see that?
If you want to catch
the Mafia, do as I say.
What do we do?
You'll take turns saying
who you think is Mafia,
and I'll pick for you.
Why do you get to decide?
We should decide together.
Yes. Who do you think you are?
Didn't you see Woo Ram
try to kill me last night?
Who other than me is definitely Citizen?
I think...
Mafia's among the people
who voted for me yesterday.
No.
We're really not Mafia.
You sided with Woo Ram
and tried to kill me.
What clearer evidence is there?
We really didn't know.
Don't judge based on last night.
Then what should I judge you on?
You're the only people who voted for me.
Is that it?
Your logic is crap.
- Hey.
- What?
Stop it.
What about Ji Soo, then?
Why kill someone we were all friends with?
We had no reason to.
Who cares how close you
are when you could die?
Wasn't Ji Soo a Doctor?
Read the notice properly.
It says she was a Citizen.
Yu Jun must be the Doctor.
He pretended not to be.
Yesterday,
the Police used their Skill,
so why didn't the Doctor?
Yes. If they'd used their Skill,
Ji Soo could've lived.
On the third floor, weren't
Ji Soo and Yu Jun alone?
Then why kill just Ji Soo?
Could Cha Yu Jun be Mafia?
Darn it.
He killed his girlfriend?
That's really freaky if it's true.
Ji Soo did give him a hard time.
Always telling him off.
You lot are so frustrating.
I'll pick someone for you.
He thinks he's in charge.
Kim Jun Hee's Mafia.
You can tell when he got the ax
and went crazy to save Woo Ram.
He did it to save him
thinking he was a Citizen.
We were all betrayed by someone we trusted.
He really got us good.
We're victims too.
Yes. I don't think we should vote
for Jun Hee just because of that.
Then shall I pick one of you?
Go and vote already.
Hey.
Don't you know about presuming innocence?
Don't insist when you don't have proof.
What?
We're not voting for whom you dislike most.
This is just like a witch hunt.
My hunch is proof, darn it.
Is there proof he's not Mafia?
There isn't.
Proof?
There's proof.
There's a surveillance
room in the basement.
I'm sure everything was filmed.
We can get the Mafia in one go.
That's awesome.
Mensa, work faster. You're so darn slow.
It's "Mensan."
I just turned it on. Wait.
What's this? Hang on.
What's wrong?
There are no files. Someone deleted them.
Are they saved somewhere else? Look again.
It's not that. They're really gone.
It wasn't even formatted automatically.
Someone deleted them on purpose.
Lee Yoon Seo. What's going on?
You trolled us all.
Gosh, you Mafia jerks.
Nice team-play. Did you delete them?
It's not like that.
As if it isn't.
You and Jun Hee defended
Woo Ram from the start.
You showed up late because
you deleted the files.
You're just pretending you didn't.
- It's not like that!
- Lee Yoon Seo.
How did you know you could
see the footage from here?
What?
You knew because you went
looking to delete the files.
No?
What...
I came across this place by chance.
If she'd deleted the files, why
would she have brought us here?
Yes. And she doesn't know how to do this.
It's game over.
- I voted.
- Hey, Ko Kyung Jun!
- Ko Kyung Jun...
- Wait.
Voted for Lee Yoon Seo.
Kim Jin Ha, Shin Seung Bin...
voted for Lee Yoon Seo.
Cha Yu Jun voted for Lee Yoon Seo.
Guys, wait.
I'm really a Citizen.
I'll prove that I am.
Give me until today. Please.
Yoon Seo really isn't Mafia.
I'll restore the files.
Give me some time.
Yes. We can vote later at night.
Right.
Once the files are restored,
we'll know who's Mafia.
Okay.
Let's go.
Yoon Seo.
I'll restore the files by 11pm.
Let's vote then.
So, we're gathering at 11pm?
Yes. She'll restore the
footage and show us.
She's doing all she can to stall.
It would be awesome if
something was filmed.
Yes. That would be clear-cut.
(Jang Hyun Ho)
I should've voted for Yoon Seo then.
Why?
Because of Woo Ram,
Kyung Jun suspects us too.
It's easiest to go with the flow.
Shall we just vote now?
What if we do and she's a Citizen?
What?
That makes us murderers.
What'll you do then?
Who cares?
It can't be helped.
So what?
You'll keep doing what Kyung Jun says?
If he tells you to pick
me or Jun Hee, will you?
Hey, don't say that.
To be honest,
how do we know who's
Mafia and who's a Citizen?
So Mi, you just...
don't like Yoon Seo, that's why.
Hey.
Are you Mafia?
What?
You've been really close with
Yoon Seo and Jung Won lately.
I'm wondering if it's
because you're all Mafia.
Kim So Mi.
Stop it.
So Mi, don't go too far.
She's not doing well
because Hyun Ho's dead.
Hey, Na Hee.
Are you sulking?
Ahn Na Hee!
Jung Won.
Can you restore the files by 11pm?
No.
I can't restore them all.
I must pick a few from yesterday.
Hey. I didn't say I can't do it.
I'll restore the clip from
the third-floor hallway.
Yes. Let's not worry too much.
I'm sure Jung Won can manage.
Do you have a laptop?
Why?
Let's use yours too. Go get it.
Okay.
Hey.
I'll go check something.
Where are you going?
Keep working on this.
The security cameras were on yesterday.
I saw the guys in their rooms.
But there are no cameras in the rooms.
It's so weird.
I found this too.
Jun Hee.
I'm really not lying,
and I didn't hallucinate.
Yoon Seo.
I believe you.
Let's do all we can.
Is the room connected to something else?
I have to look again.
- Okay, let's go.
- No.
I'll go on my own. It's too narrow for you.
You'll be scared on your own.
And you'll need a witness.
I'll go in first.
Watch your step.
Jun Hee.
What would you do...
if I were Mafia?
It doesn't matter.
Why doesn't it matter?
I won't vote for you anyway.
We reached the end.
It's blocked.
What? Look carefully.
I fell through the floor.
The floor's firm too.
It's weird, you know.
Ever since I came here,
I've been dreaming of myself dying.
It was just a dream.
But I was scared.
I often got sick.
So I...
did think...
I might die.
But dying here like this?
I've never imagined it.
Jun Hee.
I don't want to die.
You won't die.
I'll never let you die.
We should go home. Don't
you want to go home?
I do.
I want to go home.
Yes.
And don't worry even if we
can't restore the footage.
We can find another way.
Yoon Seo.
Do you think there will be another proof?
Another proof?
(Rebuild communication.)
What is it?
Blood.
I saw it in a book.
You can see it with this light.
What?
The door is locked.
So they would've broken it with an ax.
This blood must be Woo
Ram's that was on the ax.
His blood might be on the person
who touched the ax as well.
Then...
it means we can find who
it is if we check everyone.
But his blood got splashed on me
when I was next to him yesterday.
The same thing might've
happened to the other guys too.
So we can't be sure.
Even if there's blood on them,
we don't know if it's Woo Ram's.
Innocent people might be
suspected for no reason.
I think we can restore the security
camera footage on the third floor.
- It's done.
- What?
The footage from yesterday is restored.
All we should do is check
who entered Ji Soo's room.
Where is it?
It's glitching.
- What's this?
- What's the matter?
What is wrong?
- It's dangerous.
- No.
- My gosh.
- What's this?
- No.
- Darn it.
- Move over.
- It's fire.
Were you freaking trying
to burn all of us to death?
It really wasn't me.
Hey. What's that?
- Darn it.
- Oh, no.
What's that? Is that real?
I think there really is a ghost.
This is unbelievable.
Look.
Look at this.
She's the ghost in the footage.
I think...
there really is something other than us.
That ghost must have to do
something with the Mafia Game.
Stop with your nonsense.
It's a fake video you guys made.
You idiot. Look at the timecode.
It's filming in real time.
Then...
will you play the game that
kills people as they say?
What if you win?
Do you think we can survive
and get out of here?
Do you still think you can even
after seeing how others died?
Get a grip.
We should find out who
made us play the game.
If we only find the relation...
between the ghost and the Mafia Game,
we might be able to get
out of here for real.
(No diving)
Hey. It's almost midnight.
Will you not vote?
How about we vote...
in a different way?
Jun Hee, we don't have time right now.
How can we do it differently?
You almost killed us all. What
nonsense are you saying now?
Right, you stupid class president.
We almost died because we listened to you.
We can listen to him
first before we decide.
What is it? Tell us.
Out of 13 votes, Yoon Seo received 4.
You die when the majority votes for you.
Otherwise, you won't die.
We can divide the remaining votes...
so that she isn't voted by the majority.
So you want to make another person
receive four votes like Yoon Seo...
to make it a tie.
Yes.
That way, all of us will vote...
without abstaining.
But...
who will become the one to
receive the same number of votes?
Vote for me.
What?
(Will you vote for Kim Jun Hee?)
(Jin Da Bum voted for Kim Jun Hee.)
Jin Da Bum...
voted for Kim Jun Hee.
- Voted.
- Kim Jun Hee...
voted for Oh Jung Won.
- Voted.
- For...
- Voted for Nam Yeon Woo.
- Nam Yeon Woo...
voted for Im Eun Chan.
Ahn Na Hee and Oh Jung Won...
voted for Kim Jun Hee.
Lee Yoon Seo...
A minute left to vote.
Choi Mi Na voted for Kim So Mi.
Kim So Mi voted for Choi Mi Na.
Voting is over.
(Voting is over.)
It worked.
It worked. It actually worked!
Are you sure it worked?
- Did it really work?
- It worked.
It worked.
We did it.
Let's go.
As Lee Yoon Seo...
and Kim Jun Hee received
the same number of votes,
hold the 2nd round of voting
for the 2 for 5 minutes.
Only those who didn't vote for
either of them in the first round...
will vote again.
If they're tied again,
everyone will be executed.
They're going to kill us too?
I knew it. Let's just vote
for that scumbag and end this.
Only the five of us should vote, right?
Me, Yeon Woo, Mi Na, So Mi,
and who else is it?
The class president. He
voted for Jung Won earlier.
It means Yoon Seo received
one less vote already.
One minute has passed already.
What do we do? Who should we vote for?
(Vote)
(Will you vote for Lee Yoon Seo?)
- Hey, Kim So Mi.
- Kim So Mi...
voted for Lee Yoon Seo.
It was strange when she talked about
the ghost and dragged us into this.
We were going to vote for Yoon Seo.
Hurry up!
This is not right.
Don't vote for her.
Seriously...
Just freaking vote for anyone!
Hey.
Are you okay now?
You quit swimming because you
couldn't enter water anymore.
I'm fine. I'm all good now.
I said I was a Citizen.
It's all because of me.
I'll take the responsibility.
It's me.
I'm Mafia.
So vote for me.
Hey.
Why are you saying that?
Are you crazy?
I told you to hand in your
phones so that you can't vote.
I was the one who deleted
the security camera footage.
No.
I'm sorry.
I did it because I wanted to survive.
No.
But killing people...
I can't do it anymore.
I knew it when he was
running around with an ax.
Just vote for that jerk and end this!
Wait.
Hey. It's not you.
Why are you doing this? It's not you.
- Why are you doing this?
- Choi Mi Na...
- Hey. Don't. It's not him.
- Voted for Kim Jun Hee.
Don't do it.
Hey. It's not you.
- It's really not you.
- Im Eun Chan...
voted for Kim Jun Hee.
We should go.
- Jun Hee, it's not you.
- Nam Yeon Woo...
- voted for Kim Jun Hee.
- Please.
- Let's go.
- Don't do it.
Don't!
- Let's hurry up and go.
- Jun Hee.
Just a second.
Yoon Seo.
Jun Hee. No!
Kim Jun Hee got the most
votes and he will be executed.
No.
Jun Hee.
Let go of me.
No.
Please.
(Lee Yoon Seo)
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through
Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform
Content Production Business.)